<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Cyberfeed.io</title><link>https://cyberfeed.io/feed</link><description>Daily Cybersecurity News Aggregator</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 20:22:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>9to5Mac Happy Hour 397: iPhone 14 and Apple Watch Series 8 Apple event expectations</title><link>https://9to5mac.com/2022/09/02/9to5mac-happy-hour-397/</link><description> Zac and Benjamin get hyped for next week’s Apple event, and discuss all the last-minute expectations for the iPhone 14 and Apple Watch Series 8 and maybe the Apple Watch Pro too. Sponsored by Upside: Download the FREE Upside App and use promo code 9to5mac to get $5 or more cash back on your first purchase of $10 or more. Sponsored by Pillow: Pillow is an all-in-one sleep tracking solution to help you get a better night’s sleep. Download it from the App Store today.    more… The post 9to5Mac Happy Hour 397: iPhone 14 and Apple Watch Series 8 Apple event expectations appeared first on 9to5Mac.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 13:34:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>OBS Studio 28 with native Apple Silicon Mac support now available to everyone</title><link>https://9to5mac.com/2022/09/02/obs-studio-28-apple-silicon-mac-support/</link><description> OBS Project last month released a new beta version of the popular live streaming app OBS Studio, which has added native support for Macs with an Apple Silicon chip. The update, named OBS Studio 28, is now available as an official release to everyone.  more… The post OBS Studio 28 with native Apple Silicon Mac support now available to everyone appeared first on 9to5Mac.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 13:45:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Peak Design launches iPhone 14 event guessing game with $10k garbage bag grand prize</title><link>https://9to5mac.com/2022/09/02/peak-design-iphone-14-guessing-game-10k-prize/</link><description> Peak Design is holding a fun guessing game ahead of the “Far out” iPhone 14 event that’s set for September 7. Along with a garbage bag filled with $10,000 as the grand prize 500 others will have the chance to win a free iPhone case.  more… The post Peak Design launches iPhone 14 event guessing game with $10k garbage bag grand prize appeared first on 9to5Mac.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 14:11:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Popular anti-spam app Truecaller gets completely rebuilt with improved filters and more</title><link>https://9to5mac.com/2022/09/02/truecaller-ios-update-improved-filters/</link><description> Truecaller is a popular anti-spam app that alerts users about unwanted calls and text messages. This week, the company announced a major update for the iOS version of the app, which has been completely rebuilt with improved filters and other new features.  more… The post Popular anti-spam app Truecaller gets completely rebuilt with improved filters and more appeared first on 9to5Mac.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 15:08:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>This trick lets you visualize the new iPhone 14 cutout on your iPhone now</title><link>https://9to5mac.com/2022/09/02/see-iphone-14-cutout-on-any-iphone/</link><description> We’re days away from Apple’s “Far out” iPhone 14 event and one of the big changes is the 2022 iPhone lineup arriving with a new design for the display cutout. If you’re curious what it will look like, check out this fun trick to see iPhone 14 cutout on your iPhone now.  more… The post This trick lets you visualize the new iPhone 14 cutout on your iPhone now appeared first on 9to5Mac.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 15:56:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Poll: What are you most excited to see at Apple’s ‘Far out’ special event?</title><link>https://9to5mac.com/2022/09/02/what-are-you-excited-apples-far-out-event/</link><description> September is finally here, and we’re just a few days away from Apple’s next special event that will take place on Wednesday, September 7. Based on rumors, Apple is expected to introduce the iPhone 14 lineup in addition to at least two new Apple Watch models next week. With that in mind, what are you most excited to see at Apple’s “Far out” event?  more… The post Poll: What are you most excited to see at Apple’s ‘Far out’ special event? appeared first on 9to5Mac.</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 16:21:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Google Release Urgent Chrome Update to Patch New Zero-Day Vulnerability</title><link>https://thehackernews.com/2022/09/google-release-urgent-chrome-update-to.html</link><description>Google on Friday shipped emergency fixes to address a security vulnerability in the Chrome web browser that it said is being actively exploited in the wild. The issue, assigned the identifier CVE-2022-3075, concerns a case of insufficient data validating in Mojo, which refers to a collection of runtime libraries that provide a platform-agnostic mechanism for inter-process communication (IPC). An</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 20:56:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Samsung Admits Data Breach that Exposed Details of Some U.S. Customers</title><link>https://thehackernews.com/2022/09/samsung-admits-data-breach-that-exposed.html</link><description>South Korean chaebol Samsung on Friday said it experienced a cybersecurity incident that resulted in the unauthorized access of some customer information, the second time this year it has reported such a breach. "In late July 2022, an unauthorized third-party acquired information from some of Samsung's U.S. systems," the company disclosed in a notice. "On or around August 4, 2022, we determined</description><pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 21:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple @ Work: Accessory security comes to the Mac with macOS Ventura</title><link>https://9to5mac.com/2022/09/03/macos-accessory-security/</link><description> Apple @ Work is brought to you by Mosyle, the only Apple Unified Platform. Mosyle is the only solution that fully integrates 5 different applications on a single Apple-only platform, allowing Businesses and Schools to easily and automatically deploy, manage &amp; protect all their Apple devices . Over 32,000 organizations leverage Mosyle solutions to automate the deployment,  management and security of millions of Apple devices daily. Request a FREE account today and discover how you can put your Apple fleet on auto-pilot at a price point that is hard to believe. If you watch any movie that involves hacking or cyber crime, you’ll likely see the root of the breach as a result of some accessory plugged into a computer. Apple certainly doesn’t want macOS to be at the center of a real-life breach, so accessory management is getting an overhaul in macOS Ventura. Let’s look at macOS accessory security, and how Apple is implementing it for its device management partners.  more… The post Apple @ Work: Accessory security comes to the Mac with macOS Ventura appeared first on 9to5Mac.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 04:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Apple September 7 event: Latest rumors, iPhone 14, Apple Watch Series 8, iOS 16 release date, more</title><link>https://9to5mac.com/2022/09/03/apple-september-event-iphone-14-what-to-expect/</link><description> On September 7, Apple will hold its traditional event. Although there are several products the company could be readying, two of them people are expecting the most: the iPhone 14 series and the Apple Watch Series 8. Here’s what Apple could announce at its “Far Out” September event.  more… The post Apple September 7 event: Latest rumors, iPhone 14, Apple Watch Series 8, iOS 16 release date, more appeared first on 9to5Mac.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 04:31:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>iPhone’s classic battery indicator could make a comeback for iPhone 14 Pro models</title><link>https://9to5mac.com/2022/09/03/iphone-14-pro-classic-battery-indicator/</link><description> In just a few days, Apple will unveil the next generation of iPhones with the iPhone 14 series. Last-minute rumors believe the company will ditch the notch for the iPhone Pro models in regard to a hole-punch + pill cutout that will look like a pill. A report acknowledges that this new design could bring back the classic battery indicator on the status bar.  more… The post iPhone’s classic battery indicator could make a comeback for iPhone 14 Pro models appeared first on 9to5Mac.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 05:23:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Report: People are more interested in buying Apple Car rather than a new Tesla</title><link>https://9to5mac.com/2022/09/03/apple-car-buying-interest-tesla/</link><description> Apple Car is, at least, a few years away from being introduced. While Project Titan is surrounded by controversies, top executives leaving, and complete turnovers on what the Apple Car will ultimately be, a survey indicates that US customers are more interested in buying a car from the Cupertino company rather than buying a new Ford or Tesla.  more… The post Report: People are more interested in buying Apple Car rather than a new Tesla appeared first on 9to5Mac.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 05:52:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The good news about Apple’s rumored iPhone 14 Pro price hike</title><link>https://9to5mac.com/2022/09/03/iphone-14-price-increase/</link><description> The iPhone 14 will be even more expensive than its predecessor, at least according to a new report from analyst Ming-Chi Kuo. If he’s to be believed, the iPhone 14 Pro and iPhone 14 Pro Max will both be more expensive than their predecessors.  But the addition of a new iPhone 14 Max this year means there are some important details to keep in mind.  more… The post The good news about Apple’s rumored iPhone 14 Pro price hike appeared first on 9to5Mac.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 Sep 2022 09:50:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Pros and Cons of Managed Firewalls</title><link>https://www.darkreading.com/attacks-breaches/the-pros-and-cons-of-managed-firewalls</link><description>Managed firewalls are increasingly popular. This post examines the strengths and weaknesses of managed firewalls to help your team decide on the right approach.</description><pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2022 11:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>